[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Which of the following is not a JavaScript Scope type?",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "content": "Global Scope"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "content": "Universal Scope"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "content": "Block Scope"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "content": "Function Scope"
      }
    ],
    "correctOption": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What are values of sum1 and sum2?",
    "code": "  let num1 = 5;\n  let num2 = 5;\n\n  const f = () => {\n    num1 = 3;\n    let num2 = 3;\n    return num1 + num2;\n  };\n\n  const sum1 = f();\n  const sum2 = num1 + num2;",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "content": "10 10"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "content": "6 10"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "content": "6 8"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "content": "8 6"
      }
    ],
    "correctOption": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which will be the result of the following expression?",
    "code": "(3 < 2 < 1) + 1",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "content": "2"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "content": "NaN"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "content": "1"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "content": "null"
      }
    ],
    "correctOption": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Which will be the output of the following code snippet? Guess the order.",
    "code": "  setTimeout(() => console.log(1), 1000);\n  setTimeout(() => console.log(2), \"1000\");\n  setTimeout(() => console.log(3));\n  setTimeout(() => console.log(4), 2000);\n  setTimeout(() => console.log(5), \"1000ms\");\n  console.log(6);",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "content": "6 1 2 3 4 5"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "content": "6 3 4 1 2 5"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "content": "6 3 5 1 2 4"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "content": "3 6 1 2 5 4"
      }
    ],
    "correctOption": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What are the final values of arr1 and arr2",
    "code": "  let arr1 = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5];\n  let arr2 = arr1.splice(2, 2, 6, 7);",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "content": "[1, 2, 3, 4, 5]  [1, 2, 3, 4, 5]"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "content": "[1, 2, 3, 4, 5]  [1, 2, 6, 7, 5]"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "content": "[1, 2, 6, 7, 5]  [1, 2, 6, 7, 5]"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "content": "[1, 2, 6, 7, 5]  [3, 4]"
      }
    ],
    "correctOption": 4
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Which will be the value of result.",
    "code": " const result = 1 + 1 + \"1\" + (2 + 3);",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "content": "8"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "content": "NaN"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "content": "\"11123\""
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "content": "\"215\""
      }
    ],
    "correctOption": 4
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Which will be the output of the following code snippet?",
    "code": "  const user = {\n    name: \"John\",\n    age: 5,\n    isAdult: false,\n  };\n\n  Object.keys(user);",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "content": "[\"name\", \"age\", \"isAdult\"]"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "content": "[\"John\", 5, false]"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "content": "[ [\"name\", \"John\"], [\"age\", 5], [\"isAdult\", false] ]"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "content": "[\"name\", \"John\"]"
      }
    ],
    "correctOption": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "The promise is in one of these states except.",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "content": "pending"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "content": "fulfilled"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "content": "succeeded"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "content": "rejected"
      }
    ],
    "correctOption": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Which will be the output of the following code snippet? Guess the order.",
    "code": "  let promise = new Promise((resolve) => {\n    setTimeout(() => console.log(1));\n    resolve(2);\n    console.log(3);\n  });\n\n  promise.then((res) => {\n    console.log(res);\n  });",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "content": "1 2 3"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "content": "3 1 2"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "content": "3 2 1"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "content": "1 3 2"
      }
    ],
    "correctOption": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which will be the output of the following code snippet?",
    "code": "  function f() {\n    console.log(a);\n    var a = 5;\n    console.log(a);\n  }\n\n  f();",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "content": "undefined 5"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "content": "5 5"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "content": "ReferenceError"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "content": "undefined undefined"
      }
    ],
    "correctOption": 1
  }
]
